CORNELIU MAVRODI

Android Developer

176 41 66 41 06 · CorneliuM@tutanota.com · Linkedin · Portfolio · Unterkirnach, Germany

Summary

I'm an aspiring Android developer with a deep passion for building software that extends beyond mobile platforms. With four applications published on Google Play and 1 year + of experience using Android SDK and Kotlin, I thrive on the satisfaction of knowing that my creations are used and appreciated by people. Collaboration and teamwork are fundamental principles in my approach to development, and I strongly advocate for sound architectural design in crafting applications.

Experience

Android Developer

2022 - ONGOING

Malferma Mondo, Google Play

Unterkirnach, Germany

- Worked with Kotlin, Jetpack Compose, Room, Console Google Play, Firebase, DI, CI, Git, GitHub Actions, MVVM.
- · Designed, developed, published 4 Application on Google Play.
- Two of the published applications require at least one update per year. I implemented a python script to simplify writing new data in the XML resources.
- Upgraded the media and descriptions of my four applications, which increased their average conversion rate by 30%.

Software Engineer

2022 - 2023

K+k information services GmbH

Fellbach, Germany

- · Worked with C# .Net, VBA, Scrum.
- Improved the delivery of updates to client devices, reducing the number of failures to almost zero
- Created a new decompose script that takes 10 times less time to run, averaging 20 seconds, saving each engineer up to an hour per day.
- After refactoring VBA legacy code and using OOP principle, time consumption by implementing new features decreased in half.

Trainee 2021 – 2022

K+k information services GmbH

Fellbach, Germany

- Worked with Kotlin, JavaScript, C# .Net, DI.
- · Implemented an Authorization system for an existing Rest API Application using JWT.
- Developed a copy of intern used iOS Application for android platform using Android SDK, Kotlin, Room, XML.

Paketzusteller 2017 – 2018

DPD & DHL VS- Schwenningen, Germany

Education

IHK, IT specialist application development

2020 - 2022

GFN GmbH

Donaueschingen, Germany

Architecture and Urbanism

2008 - 2012

Technical University of Moldova

Chişinău, Republic of Moldova

Courses & Certificates

Android Jetpack 2023

Udemy

| UI UX De | esign Patterns | | | | 2023 | |
|--|--|--------|--|--|----------------------------------|--|
| Agile Scrum Foundation EXIN German Language Cours B1 & B2 & Integration Cours Volkshochschule | | | | 2021 | | |
| | | | | 2019 – 2020 Villingen – Schwenningen, Germany | | |
| | al Support Fundamentals & and Bytes of Computer Netv | vorkir | ng | | 2018 | |
| | | | Skills – Soft | | | |
| • | Quality control Detail oriented | • | Analytical thinking Self-motivation | • | Goal orientation Adaptability | |
| | | | Skills – Hard | | | |
| • | Android SDK Jetpack Console Google Play C# | • | Kotlin Compose Git MVVM Languages | • | Room Rest API CI UI | |
| - Englis | h: B1 – German: B2 | | Romanian: Mother to | naue | - Russian: Proficient | |
| Liigiio | ii. Di German. D2 | | terests & Hobbies | nigue | Russian. Frontiern | |
| | | | (• • • | Ć¢ | | |

Games

Piano

Hike

Table Tennis